# Francis Emmanuel

Software Engineer / website developer

## Profile

I'm a passionate web developer and full stack engineer with one year of experience under my belt. My proudest achievement? Crafting dynamic, user-friendly websites that leave a lasting impact. My top qualities include adaptability, problem-solving, and a relentless drive for innovation. Let's turn your web dreams into reality!

# Employment History

Staff manager at Nengi's place restaurant, Abuja

January 2019 — January 2020

Administrator at Tams Express logistics, Abuja

February 2021 — December 2021

Tutor at Build Brothers, Makurdi

September 2023 — Present

### Education

Primary education, Brighter light academy, Abuja

April 2005 - September 2010

Graduated with honors

Basic Education Certificate Examination, Royal model academy , Abuja

January 2010 — December 2013

Graduated with BECE certificate

Senior school certificate examination , Royal model academy , Abuja

January 2014 — June 2017

Graduated with an SSCE certificate

Full stack web development, Build brothers hub, Makurdi

February 2023 — September 2023

#### **Details**

Abuja

Nigeria

08104101868

francemma20@gmail.com

#### Links

X (formerly known as twitter)

Portfolio

LinkedIn

GitHub

#### **Skills**

Adaptability

Fast Learner

Computer Skills

Ability to Work Under

Pressure

**Customer Service** 

Communication Skills

Leadership and Teamwork

#### **Hobbies**

Listening to music Watching anime Working out Studying